## Michelle

# Full Stack Developer

■ keysven0@gmail.com 
 ▼ Tampines, Singapore

#### **Profile**

I am an enthusiastic, intelligent, productive Fullstack Developer specializing in the test-driven development and design, highly performant web applications with 7 years of experience.

Always focus on improving my coding skills, design patterns and principles up-to -date, build products more efficient, user-friendly and well-documented.

#### **Skills**

**Frontend** 

Html, CSS/SCSS, Javascript, JSX, Typescript, React, Vue, ¡Query, Nextjs

**Database** 

MySQL, PostgreSQL, Oracle, MongoDB, Firebase

**Backend** 

Node, Express, Nestjs Django, Flask PHP, Laravel, CI, RUby

**Others** 

AWS: S3 bucket, AWS managed blockchain, EC2,

**AWS IOT** 

AI: Stable Diffusion, DALL-E

### **Professional Experience**

10/2023 - present

**Freelancer**, *Freelancer* 

Spearheaded 3 projects that improved the company's revenue by

\$500K through automation and usability improvements ( React,

Redux, Redux-Saga)

 Mentored 2 interns in front-end development, focusing on HTML,

CSS, JavaScript, React, MUI, and taught them best practices over a

period of 6 months.

- Took a responsibility for conducting R&D tasks related to blockchain technology within the company (consensus, crypto tax, crypto payment integration, apollo)
- Attended 100+ scrum meetings to receive daily, weekly tasks and resolve challenges.

07/2021 - 09/2023

Full Stack Developer, Scorpioi information technology Pte Ltd

- Developed 12+ original e-commerce website and web applications, encompassing design, coding, testing, and maintenance whilst supervising a team of 8 web developers (React, Node, MongoDB).
- Created an automated testing framework for CI/CD to improve the average time to push new builds into production by 40%, gaining success and continuous improvements and efficiency for company operations.

Singapore, Singapore

Singapore,

Singapore

Languages		
04/2014 – 09/2017	<b>Master's degree in Engineer,</b> Computer Engineer, Singapore Institude of Technology University(SiT)	Singapore, Singapore
Education		
10/2017 – 06/2021	<ul> <li>Frontend Developer, Orfeostory Pte Ltd</li> <li>Learned organization's overall strategies, business operates, and what drives success in the business.</li> <li>Collaborated with 3 engineering and design teams to integrate external APIs into web pages and applications.</li> <li>Developed 5+ applications leveraging proficiency with HTML5, CSS3 and Javascript, following Agile, Scrum product development methodologies.</li> </ul>	Singapore, Singapore
	<ul> <li>Improved the home page views through SEO optimization, A/B testing, and conversion rate optimization. P</li> </ul>	

• Chinese

• English